<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    
    <title>JoaoPires.com</title>
    
    
    <description>Here&apos;s what I&apos;m up to...</description>
    
    <link>http://localhost:4000/</link>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:4000/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
      <item>
        <title>Swift Library - Portugal Trains</title>
        <description>
          A Swift Library to query the Infraestruturas de Portugal (IP) API. - 
          In the process of rebuilding my App Portfolio, I’ve been rewriting some abandoned apps I have. The first app in my sight is called redE - Comboios de Portugal. This app allowed the users to check the time tables of trains in a given train station in almost real time....
        </description>
        <pubDate>Sun, 09 Jan 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/2022-01-09-Portugal-Trains-Library/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/2022-01-09-Portugal-Trains-Library/</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Minimalist to a fault</title>
        <description>
          From minimal to none… - 
          I’ve been a fan of minimalism for years. Not only the aesthetics but also the life philosophy. At one point in my life I could fit everything I owned in a car - granted, I was only 20 at the time. I always try to avoid being extreme in anything...
        </description>
        <pubDate>Sat, 08 Jan 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/2022-01-08-minimalist-to-a-fault/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/2022-01-08-minimalist-to-a-fault/</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>My Troubled Relationship With Social Media</title>
        <description>
          I deleted Facebook years ago, but still use twitter, sometimes… - 
          When Social Media first started, in the early 2000’s, I was all over it. Being a tech geek, Myspace, Hi5 and, Orkut where all the rage for me at the time. Then came Facebook, Twitter and Instagram and for a brief moment Google+. They we’re more polished services, and attracted...
        </description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 20 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/2021-04-20-on-social-media/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/2021-04-20-on-social-media/</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Ares – RSS Reader</title>
        <description>
          Today, after a few days of struggle with AppStore review, Ares, my most recent app was finally released - 
          Before Today I did Ares as a personal project. Last time I published an App in my own name to the AppStore was in 2019. I wasn’t happy with it then, and I sure wasn’t happy with it last month when I finally decided to remove it. Throughout the years...
        </description>
        <pubDate>Sun, 18 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/2021-04-18-ares-rss-reader/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/2021-04-18-ares-rss-reader/</guid>
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
